《烈探雷徹》前情提要
Previously on Reacher...
不管你朋友卷入的是什么事 其金額都大到害死了他們
Well, whatever your friends were involved in was big enough to get them killed.
我招募的托尼斯旺 絕對不可能參與此事
There's no way the Tony Swan I recruited is a part of this.
看來斯旺的職位是安全總監助理
Seems Swan's title was assistant director of security.
“謝恩蘭斯頓 安全總監”
"Shane Langston. Director of Security."
也許在大西洋城 跟我通話的就是這個人
Maybe he's the guy I got on the phone in Atlantic City.
我們得跟馬爾科姆拉沃伊談談
We need to talk to Malcolm Lavoy.
我們永遠沒法接近參議員 從他口中套話
We'll never get close enough to a senator to find out what he may or may not know.
我們不需要接近他 丹尼爾博伊德 拉沃伊參議員的立法主任
Oh, we don't need to. Daniel Boyd, Senator Lavoy's legislative director.
小翅膀可以擊中空中的任何物體
Little Wing can knock anything out of the sky.
新時代有兩個基地
New Age has two bases.
軟件是在紐約開發的 硬件是在丹佛的制造工廠制造的
Software made in New York, hardware at a manufacturing plant in Denver.
我們的指令是什么
What are our directives?
你和迪克森去丹佛 奧唐納和我會去華盛頓特區
You and Dixon go to Denver. O'Donnell and I will head down to D.C.
我想去國土安全局 看看他們是否知道AM的事
Want to swing by Homeland, see what they know about A.M.
給馬備好鞍
Saddle up...
因為我們要去做一大堆牛仔的事
...'cause we're about to do a whole lot of cowboy shit.
再見
別鬧了
Quit it!
我會抓住你的
I'm gonna get you!
不 你抓不到的
No, you're not.
別再丟我的泰迪熊了 否則我會...
Don't drop my teddy ever again or I will...
...你的臉
...at your face.
住手
Stop it!
你帶腎上腺素筆了嗎
You got the EpiPens?
- 當然帶了 - 伍比呢
- Yes, of course. - And woobie?
伍比毯 熊貓朋友 猴子林賽 全都裝好了
Woobie, Panda-pal, Lindsay the Monkey, they're all packed.
帶上一次性手機 別跟任何人聯系 不要找你父母
Grab the burner phone. No contact with anyone. Not your parents,
而且千萬別聯系你姐姐 她什么都往臉書上發
and definitely not your sister. She puts everything on Facebook.
我知道這一套
I know the drill.
去阿什維爾 帶男孩們過去 那里有很多事做
Go to Asheville. Take the boys. Plenty for you to do there.
那是旅游勝地 你會融入其中
It's touristy. You'll blend in.
用現金和現收現付信用卡
Use cash and this pay-as-you-go credit card.
按從一到十打分 情況有多糟
Scale of one to ten, how bad is this?
他們不會去找你們的
They're not gonna come after you.
我們只是謹慎行事 額外小心
We're just playing it safe. Belts and suspenders.
按從一到十打分
One to ten.
對于你們來說 最多四分
For you guys? Four, tops.
那你呢
How about you?
我們正在處理一些相當壞的家伙
Well, we're dealing with some pretty bad guys, but...
但我有朋友在身邊 我們會沒事的
I got the gang with me. We'll be fine.
過幾天就結束了
It'll be over in a couple of days, promise.
我得讓孩子做好準備
I got to get the baby ready.
就像上次一樣
把我的泰迪熊還給我
Give my tie back!
我需要你們去...
I need...
她并不驚慌
She doesn't panic.
...去挑你們的衣服
既來之 則安之
Accepts reality on reality's terms.
她是急診室護士 和芝加哥消防隊長的女兒
Daughter of an ER nurse, Chicago fire chief.
非常堅強
Tough as they come.
漂亮 堅強 聰明
Beautiful, tough, smart.
她打賭輸了才嫁給你的
She lose a bet?
這就是我在做的
...dinner. That's what I'm making.
如果當初有人問我 你的結局會是怎樣
If someone asked me back in the day where I thought you'd wind up,
我會預測你因為淋病慢慢死去
I'd have predicted a slow death from gonorrhea
還會有六個女朋友 為了一輛04年的馬自達大打出手
and a half dozen girlfriends fighting over an '04 Miata.
是啊 原來我并不想要 世界上的每一個女孩
Yeah, well, turns out I didn't want every girl in the world,
只想要對的那個
just the right one.
你想稍微冷靜一下嗎
內格利和迪克森剛到丹佛的工廠
Neagley and Dixon just got to the Denver plant.
很好 她們也許能拿到那些導彈
Good. Maybe they get ahold of those missiles
你的家人就不必離開太久
and your family won't have to be gone long.
你真慢
You're a slowpoke.
好的
Okay.
離開幾天沒關系
A few days wouldn't hurt.
我會的
I will.
科羅拉多州丹佛
國防合約管理局一個月前來過這里
The DCMA was here a month ago.
是啊 現在我們又回來了
Yeah, and now we're back.
我們可是政府監管的“皰疹” 總是神出鬼沒
We're the cold sores of government oversight.
現在 請把你們的領班叫來
Now, if you please? Your foreman?
新時代科技 配送倉庫
在這里等著
Wait here.
真是讓我驚嘆不已 你拿著寫字板 表現自然
Never ceases to amaze me how far you can get into a place
就好像你就應該在那兒一樣
if you just act like you're supposed to be there and carry a clipboard.
你覺得怎么樣
How you feeling?
疼
Sore.
穿著高跟鞋打架 是需要一段時間適應的
Well, fighting in heels takes some getting used to.
穿高跟鞋走路 也需要一段時間適應 我從來沒穿過
Walking in heels takes some getting used to. Never wore 'em.
你之前從來不穿高跟鞋
You never wore heels?
不穿
Nope.
連學校舞會上都不穿
Not even to a school dance?
從沒去過
Never went to one.
我不學習 或者不照顧我爸的時候 我得去工作
When I wasn't studying or taking care of my dad, I had to work.
也就是糟糕的音樂 溫暖的酒水 以及一些摸著你的黏糊糊的手
Well, bad music, warm punch and some clammy hands feeling you up...
你并沒有錯過太多
you didn't miss much.
沒人跟我說你們要來檢查
Nobody told me about this.
如果我們提前通知就不是突擊檢查了
Wouldn't be a surprise inspection if we called ahead.
山姆大叔想確定 你們把錢用在了正道上
Uncle Sam wants to make sure you're using his money wisely.
所以我們來看看小翅膀肩扛式發射器
So we're here to take a look at Little Wing shoulder-fired launchers and missiles.
以及導彈 檢查它們的規格和制造協議
The specs, the manufacturing protocols,
訂單以及交貨時間表
the order and delivery schedules...
交貨時間表
Delivery schedule?
交貨時間就在十分鐘前
Ten minutes ago. That's the delivery schedule.
所有貨物剛運出去
The whole lot just went out the door.
總共650個
All 650 of them.
650?
這是相關文件
Here's the paperwork.
如果有人先給我打電話 我本可以推遲交貨 給你們留著
If someone had called me first, I'd have held them for you.
- 糟了 - 是啊
- Shit. - Yeah.
嘿
Hey, there.
你需要幫忙嗎
You need an extra set of hands?
我需要的
What I need
是你的卡車
is your truck.
爆炸槍彈
一切按計劃進行中
We're in business.
匿名來電
告訴我好消息吧
Give me good news.
GPS追蹤器完成了其使命 你在新時代的同事們還不錯
GPS tracker did the job. Your associates at New Age came through.
但是我殺了司機 他們可能會傷心
They might be upset I killed the driver, though.
只要他們能拿到錢就不會在意
Oh, they won't care so long as they get paid.
永遠不要低估貪婪的力量
Never underestimate the power of greed.
- 換車上路吧 - 好的
Switch the trailers and get on the road. Will do.
我們紐約見
Meet you in New York.
阿扎里馬哈茂德
這里這個名字
This name, right here...
阿扎里馬哈茂德
...Azhari Mahmoud.
所以我們在丹佛 追捕的那個阿倫米克洛斯
So, the Aaron Miklos we were chasing down in Denver,
就是馬哈茂德
that was Mahmoud?
是的 我們一直叫他“AM”
Yeah, we've been calling him "A.M."
這家伙很聰明 從未被捕 也沒有照片
Guy's smart. Never been caught, no photos.
我們甚至都不確定他的國籍
Hell, we're not even sure what nationality he is.
從我們對他僅有的了解來看
From the little bit we know of him,
他可以偽裝成中美洲人
he can supposedly pass for Central American,
意大利人 希臘人 中東人...
Italian, Greek, Middle Eastern.
他如幽靈一般
He's a ghost.
我們有三段他的 簡短且無關痛癢的錄音
We have three short, innocuous recordings of him.
音頻鑒定部證實是同一個人
Audio forensics matched it as the same guy.
他每次都會使用不同的身份
Each time, he's using a different identity.
意識形態呢
Ideology?
沒有政治或宗教背景
No political or religious affiliations.
對他而言 唯有金錢才是上帝 他為出價最高的人工作
His only god is money, and he works for the highest bidder.
他會接洽壞人 為他們提供做壞事所需的工具
He hooks up bad actors with the tools they need for bad actions.
他在六年前第一次 出現在我們的視線中
First popped up on our radar six years ago.
在恐怖分子試圖 獲取實驗神經毒氣罐的時候
Terrorist cell caught trying to acquire tanks of experimental nerve gas.
我們逮捕了整個團隊
We scooped up the whole lot.
所有人 除了馬哈茂德
All of them except Mahmoud.
不管他叫什么
Or whatever his name is.
幽靈
Ghost.
這次購買本來應該用無記名債券
This buy was supposed to happen with bearer bonds.
是的 逃稅者 洗錢者 和其他各種混蛋的
Yeah, financial instrument of choice for tax evaders,
首選金融工具
money launderers and other assorted assholes.
美國財政部在80年代 就停止發行這些債券了
The U.S. Treasury stopped issuing those in the '80s.
有些國家仍在使用 那些是盧森堡的
Some countries still use them. Those were from Luxembourg.
像AM這么謹慎的人 會使用無記名債券
Someone as cautious as A.M. would use bearer bonds.
如果發行量足夠大
If issued in large enough amounts,
你可以用公文包 攜帶一筆無法追蹤的財富
you can carry an untraceable fortune in a briefcase.
價值六千五百萬
65 million worth.
那就是問題所在
That's the problem.
你帶著一張無記名債券 就像帶著一百萬美元的鈔票
You hold a bearer bond, that's like carrying a million dollar bill.
它歸持有者所有
The bearer owns it.
所以AM不可能 讓除他以外的任何人運送酬勞
So no way A.M. lets anyone deliver payment but him.
這就是他的弱點
That's where he's vulnerable.
就像你哥哥一樣
Just like your brother.
當年我們辦案的時候 我問了喬
Back when we worked the case, I asked Joe
一些財務方面的問題
some questions of the financial side of things.
他也是你這么說的
He said same thing you just did.
運送酬勞的會是AM 不會是其他人
A.M. will be the delivery boy. No one else.
好的 我們給你們 看了我們掌握的信息
Okay. We showed you ours.
現在輪到你們了
Now it's your turn.
我們還在整理中
We're still piecing it together, but, uh...
但我們向你們保證 等時機成熟
we give you our word, when this bird's cooked,
- 我們會聯系你們 - 我保證
- we'll reach out. - And you have my word
我們不會再讓這家伙 逃出我們的手掌心
we won't let this guy slip through our fingers again.
AM和他的所有同伙
A.M. and everyone working with him
都將受到法律的最大制裁
will be prosecuted to the fullest extent of the law.
除非我們先把他們都殺了
Unless we kill them all first.
謝謝你們
Thanks, guys.
跟他哥哥一樣
Just like his brother.
烈探雷徹
第二季第五集
本WEB版外掛字幕由  風吹來的那片云  雙語合并
18輪車在這路上開不快的
18-wheelers can't go that fast on these roads.
我們有機會趕上他們
We've got a decent shot at catching them.
是啊 尤其是他們中途停車了
Yeah, especially if they come to a stop.
這些人是誰
Who are these guys?
會告訴我們卡車壞了的人
They're the guys who are gonna tell us the truck broke down
而且他們不得不 打電話叫另一個人來取車
and they had to call another one to come pick up the trailer.
但第二輛卡車不可能 在我們之前趕到
But no way a second truck got here before us.
不
No.
這是劫車
This is a hijacking.
有沒有可能你是錯的
Any chance you're wrong?
我沒錯 他們怎么知道我們是誰
I'm not wrong! How the fuck did they know who we are?
領班肯定給新時代打電話 說了兩個政府檢查員的事
Foreman must've called New Age about two government inspectors.
蘭斯頓發現后給這些混蛋打了電話
Langston finds out and calls these dickheads.
什么鬼
The fuck?
我覺得我們干掉他了
I think we got him.
是啊
Yeah.
看來我們還打中了 一個前胎和一個油箱
Also looks like we got a front tire and gas tank.
- 我們離不開了 - 不 我去報警
- We're not getting out of here. - No. I'll call the cops.
匿名報警
Make it anonymous.
收到
Copy that.
幫我個忙 拿一下清單 我們需要把車牌取下來
Do me a favor, grab the manifest. We need the license plate off of it.
天啊
Oh, shit.
怎么了 內格利
What's up, Neagley?
其實有很多事
Hell of a lot, actually.
我們得說快點 因為警察 正在趕來統計尸體數量的路上
We got to talk fast, because cops are on the way to a body count
我們得拉開距離
and we got to put some distance between us and them.
有什么能證明你們在現場的東西嗎
Anything to put you at the scene?
租的車
Rental car.
它被射穿了 是用迪克森的假身份證租的
It was shot to hell, but it was rented with Dixon's fake ID.
我們把它燒了 以免留下指紋和DNA
We torched it to get rid of prints and DNA.
很好 所以發生了什么
Good. So what happened out there?
你想聽壞消息 還是更壞的消息
You want the bad news or the worse news?
讓我們大吃一驚吧
Surprise us.
一輛新時代的卡車 連同其運載的650枚導彈全被劫持了
Well, a New Age truck with all 650 missiles in it was hijacked.
- 希望那是更壞的消息 - 恐怕不能如你所愿
I hope that's the worse news. You wish.
托尼斯旺還活著
Tony Swan's alive.
- 所以那是好消息啊 - 不是
- So that's a good thing. - No.
看起來斯旺還在替新時代做事
It looks like Swan's still working with New Age.
提貨單上顯示 是斯旺簽字授權送貨
According to the bill of lading, Swan personally signed off on the shipment
然后貨物才離開工廠的
before it left the factory.
那他在丹佛
So he's in Denver?
文件上顯示他是從紐約授權的
No, the paperwork said he authorized it from New York.
所以他們偽造了他的簽名
So they forged his signature.
- 是數字指紋 - 那就是他們強迫了他
- It's a digital thumbprint. - Then they forced him.
新時代紐約分部的門上有虹膜掃描儀
New Age New York has iris scanners on the doors,
計算機是用的指紋鎖
thumbprint locks on the computers.
任何人都無法強迫托尼斯旺
There's no way that anyone could force Tony Swan
通過復雜的生物識別技術 而不引起騷亂
through that maze of biometrics without causing a huge scene.
只有一個辦法能讓他們不擔心騷亂
The only way they wouldn't worry about a ruckus
那就是讓所有一千多名員工 全都參與此事
is if all thousand-plus employees were in on this thing,
但這么大規模的陰謀的幾率...
and the odds of a conspiracy that vast are...
微乎其微
Minimal.
我知道你想相信斯旺是清白的 老大 我們都想相信
I know you want to believe Swan's clean, boss, we all do,
但就目前的情況看來不是這樣 等我們安全了再聊 好嗎
but things look the way they look. Talk when we're safe, okay?
雷徹
Reacher?
收到
Copy that.
你之前說要把他們都殺了
So what you said about killing them all...
那包括托尼斯旺嗎
...that include Tony Swan?
我要去散步
I'm going for a walk.
你們不需要這些
You boys won't be needing these.
是啊 我們這兒都是朋友
Yeah, we're all friends here.
拿走了他們的槍
Took their guns.
只要他們找不到斯旺身上的竊聽器
Long as they didn't find the wire Swan's wearing,
就一切安好
we're five by five.
就像那個惡棍說的
Like that miscreant said,
“我們這兒都是朋友”
"We're all friends here."
- 我們看看你有什么 美國兵 - 美國兵
Let's see what you got, G.I. Joe. G.I. Joe?
說山地大猩猩更貼切吧
More like Mighty Joe Young.
你想不想和這個大塊頭 擠在一個散兵坑里
How'd you like to be jammed into a foxhole with this giant motherfucker?
我們的價格比你們現在付的更優惠
We'll beat whatever price you're paying now.
我們的供應商可以從 無法談判的海外源頭
Our supplier can get you all the H you can move from an overseas source
給你們弄來 所有你們可以轉運的海洛因
that's in no position to negotiate terms.
我們把省下來的錢都給你們
We pass the savings on to you.
好的
Okay.
我們來談談價錢
Let's talk money.
他們一達成協議 我們就出動
Soon as they agree to a deal, we go.
逮捕他們 逼迫他們 他們會說出他們的貨源
Bust them, lean on them, they give up their source;
我們逮捕他們 然后全都能升職
we bust them, then we all get bumped.
胸前的綬帶和獎章就更多了
More fruit salad on our chests...
薪水支票上還會有 更多美元標志哦 兄弟
More dollar signs on our paychecks, bro.
為什么要在我們的薪水支票上 加美元標志
Why would they add dollar signs to our paychecks?
閉嘴 弗朗茨
Shut up, Franzy.
這孩子說得有道理 曼努埃爾 一個美元標志就夠了 重點是零
The kid's got a point, Manuel. You only need one dollar sign.
混蛋
Assholes.
小心 有人靠近
Heads up. We got incoming.
早該來了
About time.
110?
你之前說價格會優于我們目前的價格
You said you could beat our current price.
我給你們優惠了啊
I am beating it.
還不夠
Not by enough.
你想讓我們更換供應商 那就打動我們吧
You want us to change suppliers, motivate us.
雞肉 我說的是豬肉
This is chicken. I said pork.
好吧 105怎么樣
Okay. Fucking idiots always get it wrong. How's 105?
聽起來像是在浪費我的時間
Sounds like you're wasting my fucking time.
你還找得到這么純賣105的嗎
- You got forks? - You have another brick as pure as that for 105?
- 我見過更好的 - 胡說
Seen better. Bullshit.
我有一長串買家的名單
I got a list of other buyers a mile long.
- 我來找你是因為你的量... - 我認識你
- I came to you... - I know you.
- ...值得我花時間協商 - 你認錯人了吧
...because you purchase at a volume, which makes it worthwhile. I don't think so.
沒認錯 我從哪兒認識你的來著
Yeah, I do. Where do I know you from?
糟了
Uh-oh.
等等 可能沒什么
Hold on. Might be nothing.
- 不知道 - 我知道我們以前見過
- No idea. - Look, I have other offers coming in. - I know we've met before.
- 你能為我做什么  - 一百 要么接受 要么就算了
What can you do for me? 100. Take it or leave it.
你是前不久買我吉他的那個人
I got it. You're the guy I sold my guitar to a while back.
你把我跟其他人搞混了
You got me mixed up with somebody else.
克雷格列表網 兄弟
Craigslist, dude.
你買了我的原聲吉他
You bought my acoustic.
我們是要吃飯敘舊 還是達成協議
We gonna eat and discuss old times or are we gonna make a deal?
你們這些混蛋不想要這些東西 我們有其他地方可以賣
You assholes don't want this stuff, we got other places we can sell it.
等等 這家伙買吉他的時候
Wait a minute. Wait a minute, when this guy bought it,
他穿著憲兵的制服
he was in an Army cop uniform.
上
Fuck. Go, go, go, go.
小心
Look out!
- 叫救護車  - 別開槍
- Call an ambulance! - Don't shoot!
我們有一名軍官倒下了 需要醫療救援
We have an officer down. We need medical assistance.
- 子彈沒打中你的心臟 - 但打碎了我的鎖骨
The bullet missed your heart. But shattered my collarbone.
我有段時間彈不了吉他了
Not gonna be playing that guitar for a while.
塞翁失馬
Every cloud...
去你的
Fuck you.
嘿 你不能招惹誰
Hey, who don't you mess with?
卡車駕駛員工會
The Teamsters?
我欠你一個人情
I owe you one.
讓我猜猜
Let me guess.
政府牌照 政府制服 政府的車
Government plates, government suits, government rides.
沒想到拉沃伊議員花了這么長時間
Surprised it took Senator Lavoy this long
才查出昨晚是誰動了他的走狗
to figure out who sweated his flunky last night.
參議員有個提議給你 上車
The senator has a proposition for you. Get in.
不
No.
為什么 雷徹先生
Why not, Mr. Reacher?
叫我雷徹
Just "Reacher."
好吧 雷徹 你為什么不上車
Fine, Reacher. Why won't you get in the car?
因為他語氣不善
Because he didn't ask nicely.
好的
Okay.
哈特 那個神奇的詞是什么
Hart, what's the magic word?
請你上車
Please get in the vehicle?
我在丹佛的人帶著貨物僥幸逃脫
My man in Denver barely got away with the merchandise.
我為了實現無縫交易 付出了額外的代價
I'm paying a premium for a seamless transaction,
而且目前為止 這已經算不上是無縫交易了
and so far this has been anything but seamless.
如果這些問題持續存在 那可能得調整價格了
If these problems persist, there may have to be a price adjustment.
斯旺先生的一些老朋友 給我們帶來了麻煩
Some of Mr. Swan's old friends are causing us problems,
但沒什么是我們處理不了的
but it's nothing we can't handle.
如果你想要商品 就得遵守交易
If you want the merchandise, you honor the deal.
做你答應做的事 而我也會如此
Do what you promised and I will.
好的
Okay.
很好
Good.
你現在在哪里
Where are you now?
我就在外面
I am just outside...
不 這不可能是真的吧 “弗倫奇利克”
Oh, no, t-this can't be right. "French Lick"?
他媽的美國人
Fucking Americans.
印第安納州
Indiana.
好的 等你到達這里時 小翅膀的芯片
Okay. The Little Wing chips will be ready to install
會準備好安裝在導彈里
in the missiles by the time you get here.
斯旺先生的同事們也會處理好的
And Mr. Swan's associates will be taken care of.
計劃已經開始實施了
That plan's already in motion.
去他媽的英國佬
Fuck your king.
蠢貨
Prick.
華盛頓特區史密森國家動物園
在靈長類動物展示區的后面
Backstage at the primate exhibit?
夠夸張的
Dramatic.
我以為你們在大猩猩中間會很舒服
Thought you might feel comfortable among the gorillas.
雷徹先生 我是馬爾科姆拉沃伊
Mr. Reacher, I'm Malcolm Lavoy.
- 他更喜歡你叫他“雷徹” - 不
- He prefers just "Reacher." - No.
他必須叫我“先生”
He has to call me "Mister."
雷徹先生 很抱歉 我讓人用這種方式把你帶過來
My apologies for the manner in which you were brought in here, Mr. Reacher.
我猜你使用這個地方 是因為這是華盛頓特區為數不多的
Assume you use this location 'cause it's one of the few spots in D.C.
你可以在沒有人 監視或窺探的情況下見面的地方
where you can meet without prying eyes or surveillance bugs.
這就是為什么我任命 自己為動物園董事會成員
Mm-hmm. It's why I got myself appointed to the zoo's board.
我相信你認識我的立法主任 博伊德先生吧
Ah, I believe you know my legislative director, Mr. Boyd.
是的
Yeah,
就是他喜歡可卡因
he's the one who likes cocaine.
我知道發生了什么后
You know, when I found out what happened,
我聯系了我在局里的一個朋友
I reached out to a friend of mine at the Bureau.
想象一下博伊德知道
Imagine Boyd's embarrassment when he learned
自己一開始把我們的秘密透露給了
that the people he revealed our secrets to
非聯邦特工有多尷尬
weren't FBI agents in the first place.
監控錄像顯示你們進入了轄區
Security video showed you entering the precinct
面部識別軟件 將你和一個軍人的身份證相匹配
and facial recognition software matched you to a military ID.
杰克雷徹
Jack Reacher.
沒有中間名 西點軍校出身 兩枚銀星
No middle name. West Point, two Silver Stars,
一枚銅星 一枚紫心勛章等等
a Bronze Star, Purple Heart and so on.
放尊重點
Show some respect.
很多勛章啊 順便說一句 我想感謝你的服役
That is quite a list, and I want to thank you for your service, by the way.
你退役后 像是從人間蒸發了一樣
Seems like after you retired, you kind of fell off the face of the Earth.
除了幾年前 在佐治亞州馬格雷夫的一起事件
Except for this incident a couple years ago in Margrave, Georgia.
你被指控殺了自己的兄弟
Charged with the murder of your own brother.
你當然被無罪釋放了
You were, of course, exonerated.
然后 喬之前一直在調查的
Then a massive counterfeiting operation
一個大規模偽造行動
that Joe had been investigating
實實在在地被燒毀了
literally and figuratively burned to the ground.
現在 官方的說辭是
Now, the official story was
那都是一個菜鳥警察 和一個外地退伍軍人干的
that it was all the work of a rookie cop and an out-of-town veteran.
也就是在波士頓逮捕了 博伊德的這位外地退伍軍人
The same out-of-town veteran that arrested Boyd here in Boston.
說重點吧 這里有股猴子屎的味道
Get to the point. Smells like monkey shit in here.
雷徹先生 我知道馬格雷夫的事 是你做的
Well, I know it was you in Margrave, Mr. Reacher.
我希望針對我們目前的情況 你也能做同樣的事
I want you to do the same thing for the situation we have here.
為什么
Why?
因為在波士頓 你暗示博伊德
Because in Boston, you insinuated to Boyd
軍隊和民用飛機 可能會因為小翅膀而陷入危險
that military and civilian aircraft could be in danger due to Little Wing.
現在 我只能假設那意味著
Now, I can only assume that means that terrorists
恐怖分子對這項技術很感興趣
are interested in the tech,
正在努力獲得它
working hard to obtain it.
一旦我們確認了你的身份 我們就深入調查
See, once we identified you, we looked into things deeper
我們知道你以前的小隊又重組了
and we learned that your old unit's back together,
其中有些人死了
and some are dead.
別那么震驚 雷徹先生
Don't look so shocked, Mr. Reacher,
我是美國國會議員 我能把事情做好
I'm a U.S. congressman, I get things done.
我很震驚 是因為 美國國會議員居然還能做事
I'm shocked because a U.S. congressman got anything done.
我已經習慣了 人們的陰陽怪氣 雷徹先生
I'm used to the slings and arrows, Mr. Reacher.
我的底線是想要這個武器的人
But bottom line, the people who want this weaponry
絕對不能被允許持有該武器
can never be allowed to have it.
因為如果有人知道你從一開始
Because if anyone knew you were involved in the shady dealings
就參與了創造小翅膀的不正當交易 你就會被起訴
that created Little Wing in the first place, you'd be indicted.
除掉壞人 讓我干干凈凈的
Get rid of the bad guys, keep my hands clean.
在華盛頓 我們稱之為雙贏
In Washington, we call that a win-win.
我盡我所能 給予了我方捍衛民主所需的工具
I did what I did to give our side the tools they need to defend democracy.
我只是避免了繁文縟節 那些沒什么用 只會拖延時間
I just avoided the typical red tape that does nothing but cause the delays
造成生命損失
that cost lives.
還在這個過程中中飽私囊
And lined your pockets in the process.
再次重申 這叫雙贏
Again, win-win.
我不想讓無辜群眾因為這種武器而死
But I don't want innocent people to die because of it.
我是政客 不是怪物 雷徹先生
I'm a political animal, I'm not a monster, Mr. Reacher.
而且我不是請你幫忙
And I'm not asking for your help,
我是給你提供幫助
I'm offering you mine.
你也是那種喜歡把事情做好的人
You're the kind of man who likes to gets things done, too.
你在軍隊和馬格雷夫的記錄 證明了這一點
Your record in the military, and in Margrave, proves that.
你喜歡打亂計劃
You like to upset the apple cart.
我準備給予你所需要的一切 協助你完成這項任務
Well, I'm prepared to give you whatever you need to aid you in that endeavor.
等你完工后
And when you're done,
沒有人能證明你曾卷入過那些計劃
no one will be able to prove that you were ever near those apples in the first place.
就把這些東西砸成碎片
Just smash this thing to bits.
把這些人全都一網打盡 不遺留任何人威脅他人生命
Leave no man left standing. No one left to endanger lives.
然后你就又可以消失了 沒有人會繼續找你
And then you can disappear again. No one will go looking for you.
我們是你的朋友
Or your friends.
怎么
Yeah?
嘿 不怎么快樂的巨人
Hey, Not-So-Jolly Green Giant.
你已經把那套衣服扔了嗎
You throw away that suit yet?
沒有 怎么了
No. Why?
驗尸官終于歸還了弗朗茨的尸體
Coroner finally released Franz's body.
葬禮在明天舉行
Funeral's tomorrow.
我們得回紐約
We got to go back to New York.
葬禮
我讓我的辦公室做了一些零星的調查
Had my office make some discrete inquiries.
丹佛的警察發現了 被槍擊的卡車和被掉包的拖車
Denver sheriffs found the shot-up truck with a switched-out trailer.
- 里面什么都沒有 只有幾塊磚 - 它們完美匹配
Nothing in it but crates of bricks. Guessing they perfectly matched
發射器和導彈的重量
the weight of the launchers and the missiles.
是的 看來他們的計劃 是開車將假的貨物
Yep. It seems their plan was to drive the dummy cargo down
運送到洛杉磯港口
to the port in L.A.
然后送到菲律賓的軍事基地
And ship it to an Army base in the Philippines
或者任何那武器應該去的地方
or wherever the weapons were supposed to go.
根據我們的資料顯示 是韓國
South Korea, according to the documents we saw.
真聰明
Smart.
貨船從西海岸到那里 需要三到四周的時間
Three to four weeks for a cargo ship to get there from the West Coast,
在另一邊開箱前 沒人知道武器失蹤了
no one knows the weapons were missing till they open it up on the other end.
誰知道那要多長時間呢
And who knows how long that could be?
軍隊可能會直接將其放到倉庫 幾個月都不看它們
Army could just load it into storage and not see them again for months.
到那時 為時已晚
And by then, it's too late.
恐怖分子已經擊落了數十架飛機
Terrorists have taken down dozens of planes
而我們還不知道 他們從哪兒弄來的武器
and we have no idea where they got the firepower.
說起武器
Speaking of firepower,
有任何關于真正的導彈的 去向的線索嗎
we have any leads as to where the real missiles went?
科羅拉多州警方在丹佛外的 一塊田里發現了那輛卡車 是空的
Colorado State Police found the truck in a field outside Denver. It was empty.
根據卡車在泥土里的痕跡來看
Based on the tracks in the dirt,
他們認為一架私人飛機 連夜把武器帶走了
they think a private plane flew the weapons out overnight.
它可能會去往任何地方
Could be headed here.
自從911以后 紐約上空就一直受到了密切地監控
Since 9/11, they've kept a pretty close watch on New York's skies.
我們知道AM很謹慎
And we know A.M.'s cautious.
如果我是他
I were him,
我會把它們帶到 賓夕法尼亞州的某個小機場里
I'd fly them into some small airstrip in Pennsylvania,
也可以是新罕布什爾州 再開車將武器運到紐約
maybe New Hampshire, then drive the weapons into New York
好給它們加上小翅膀軟件
to load them up with the Little Wing software.
言之有理
That makes sense.
我們需要知道導彈 到底是在往哪兒運才能攔截它們
We need to know exactly where the missiles are headed so we can intercept them.
因為當錢易手時
'Cause when the money changes hands,
AM會到場 殺了我們的人的兇手也在
A.M. will be there, and so will the people who killed our guys.
雷徹 你看到那玩意了嗎
Reacher. You seeing this shit?
那不是那天他車里的玩具嗎
Isn't that that toy he had in his car the other day?
米奇 我的侄子也有一個
Mikey. My nephews have the same one.
這是個很棒的玩具 我們一直一起玩
It's a great toy. We play with it all the time.
我小時候 我有海王
When I was a kid, I had Aquaman.
我覺得他跟魚說話的方式太酷了
I thought it was so cool how he could talk to fish.
因為我當時也想跟我的狗說話
'Cause I wanted to talk to my dog, you know?
嘿
Hey.
我也想把這張照片給你 這是我的
I want you to have this, too. This was mine.
圣杰羅姆
Saint Jerome.
他是爸爸或媽媽去了天堂的 孩子的守護神
He's the patron saint of kids whose moms and dads go to heaven.
我希望你每晚都念
I want you to say the prayer...
這照片后面的祈禱詞
...on the back, every night.
它會讓你爸離你近點
It'll help keep your dad close.
你能做到嗎
Can you do that?
好孩子
Good boy.
你有任何需要 就給我打電話
You need anything, you call me.
白天晚上都行
Day or night.
- 謝謝 - 沒事
- Thank you. - Yeah.
來吧 米奇 葬禮要開始了
Come on, Mikey. They're just about to start.
你為什么要送玩具 給我死去的朋友的兒子
Why are you giving toys to my dead friend's son?
什么
Excuse me?
和孩子相處融洽 就能刷媽媽的好感度
Cozy up to the kid, score points with Mom.
你看到一個悲傷的寡婦 心想:“這個目標容易得手”
You see a grieving widow and think, "Easy target"?
你現在在跟我開玩笑嗎  你是想找死嗎
Are you kidding me right now? You got some kind of death wish?
有些人這么想
Some people think so.
我是來表達敬意的
I'm here to pay my respects.
為什么昨晚在波士頓 有一個摩托車團伙攻擊我
Why did a biker gang take a run at me in Boston last night?
因為你是個混蛋
'Cause you're an asshole.
可能吧 也可能是因為 我們只把我們的行蹤告訴了你
Possibly. Or maybe it's 'cause you're the only person I told  we were going there.
等等 你是想說我是黑警
Wait, wait, wait. Are you trying to say that I'm bent?
我什么都沒想說
Not trying to say anything.
你知道我為什么跟米奇說話嗎  因為我知道他在經歷什么
You know why I was talking to Mikey? Because I know what he's going through.
我知道每晚看著窗戶外面
I know what it is to look out the window every night
祈禱街上來的是自己父親的車 是什么感覺
and pray that the next set of headlights coming down the street is your father's car,
即使你知道那永遠不會發生
even though you know it'll never happen,
因為你親眼看到 羅馬諾殯儀館的那些家伙
because you saw the guys from Romano's funeral home
在他的棺材上撒土
throw dirt on his casket.
你知道失去家人是什么感覺嗎
Do you know what it is to lose family?
是啊 他們都死了 全都死了
Yeah, they're all dead. Every one of them.
而我在說你
And I was talking about you,
- 沒說你爸 - 我在說他
not your father. I'm talking about him.
我爸曾是一名警察 一個好警察
My father was a cop, a good one,
他拒絕受賄 因此被人殺害
and he refused to be on the take and they killed him for it.
聽著
Look,
我知道那是 你朋友的兒子和遺孀 我懂
I know that's your friend's son and widow. I get it.
但如果你再說我是黑警
But you call me dirty one more time,
我不在乎我們是否是站在圣母像面前
and I don't care if we're standing in front of the statue of the Holy Mother,
我會新賬老賬一起算 就在這里狠狠揍你一頓
I will give you that beating that I owe you right here.
第一 只要你想 我隨時奉陪
One, I'll take that fight any time you want.
第二
And two...
我不知道你父親的事
I didn't know that about your father.
是啊 你不知道的事可多了去了
Yeah, well, what you don't know could fill the Javits.
因為天知道你在波士頓做什么的時候
Because while you were in Boston doing God knows what,
我在忙著查新時代安保部的人
I was running those security names from New Age.
他們全都是前紐約市警察局的
All former NYPD,
全部來自第三分局
all from the 3rd precinct.
老板蘭斯頓和其他幾個人 都接受過內務部的調查
The boss, Langston and a few other guys, they were under investigation by IA.
他們提前退休了 那些指控就消失了
They took early retirement and the charges went away.
然后他們全都在新時代 找到了輕松的工作 雇傭了所有朋友
Then they all got cushy jobs at New Age, and they hired all their pals along.
整個團隊全是黑警
Whole team of bad cops?
所有人 除了你的朋友 斯旺
Everybody except your buddy Swan.
但他是唯一一個有從軍經歷
But he's the only one that has military experience
知道恐怖分子 想要哪種武器的人 所以...
to know what type of weapons terrorists want, so...
現在你在含沙射影地說 會讓我生氣的事
Now you're implying something that's pissing me off.
你不能否認這種猜想是合理的
You can't deny he makes sense for this.
根據他的背景 這一切可能都是他主使的
With his background, for all we know, he might have put the whole thing together.
所有警察 全是黑警 都是一個轄區的
All cops, all bad, all from the same precinct.
- 你審問過他們中任何人嗎  - 問不了
- You interview any of them? - Couldn't.
你在他們辦公的地方砸出了一個大洞
You turned their office into a drive-through.
他們躲起來了
They went to the ground.
他們的住處空無一人 跟托尼斯旺的住處一樣
Their places were empty, just like Tony Swan's.
你想罵某人是黑警  先查查你自己的后院吧
You want to call somebody dirty? First look in your own backyard.
因此 我們要將我們的兄弟 卡爾文弗朗茨埋葬
We therefore commit our brother Calvin Franz to the ground,
歸于大地 塵歸塵 土歸土
earth to earth, ashes to ashes, dust to dust,
讓往生者安寧
in sure and certain hope of the resurrection
讓在世者重獲解脫 阿門
to the eternal life.
阿門
Amen.
鳴槍隊 注意
Firing party, attention.
待命
Stand by.
準備
Ready.
瞄準
Aim.
開火
Fire.
準備
Ready.
瞄準 開火
Aim. Fire.
- 趴下  - 開火
- Get down! - Fire...
我保護你們 快 我們走
I got you. Come on. Let's go.
離開這里 快走
Get out of here. Go.
有人開槍 快跑
Active shooters! Run!
走
- 幾個人  - 據我所知 兩個
How many? As far as I can tell, two.
- 在路對面 - 手槍沒用 得離近點
Across the road. Handguns are useless from this distance. We got to get closer.
包抄他們 內格利和我 負責右邊的那個
Flank them. Neagley and I will take the one on the right.
你們倆負責左邊那個 上
You two take the one on the left. Go.
我們盡可能接近 還不夠
Close as we're gonna get. It's not enough.
可以等警察來
We could wait for the cops.
不能讓他們跑了 他們一聽到警笛就會散開
We can't let them get away. As soon as they hear sirens, they scatter.
好吧 我來吸引火力 你去干掉他們
All right. I'll draw their fire, you take them out.
- 我拒絕 - 你能做到
- Negative. - You can do this.
你射得很準
-You're a great shot.
但你跑得很慢
But you're a slow runner.
去你的
Fuck this.
糟了
上車
Get in!
你現在相信我了 還是饑不擇食了
So, you trust me now, or are you just desperate?
我看見你保護安吉拉和米奇 所以我猜你說的是真的
I saw you protect Angela and Mikey, so I guess you're playing it square.
但你那兒有內鬼 那是肯定的
You got a rat in your house, though, that's for sure.
媽的 拉索 開快點
Shit, Russo, it's the pedal on the right.
讓我做我的工作
Let me do my job.
抄近路
Cut the corner.
- 有路緣石 - 跳過去
- There's a curb. - Jump the curb!
你能別管我怎么開車嗎
Will you climb out of my ass?
我以為這應該是高速追逐戰
I thought this was supposed to be a high-speed pursuit.
- 我們最好的線索要被你搞丟了 - 你想來開車嗎
You're losing our best lead. You want to drive?
好啊
Yes.
嘿
Hey, hey.
- 你真他媽是個禍害  - 你開車像個瞎子一樣
You're a fucking menace, you know that? You drive like you're blind.
別開槍 我受夠了 好嗎 我受夠了
Don't shoot. I'm done. Okay? I'm done.
- 你被捕了 混蛋 - 不
You're under arrest, asshole. No.
這些人在光天化日之下 攻擊我們 還是在人多的葬禮上
These guys took a run at us in broad daylight at a crowded funeral.
他們越來越絕望了 這意味著這事快到緊要關頭了
They're getting desperate. Means this thing's coming to a head fast.
我們拘留他 他會請律師 在為時已晚前緘口不言
We take him in, he lawyers up and doesn't talk until it's too late
恐怖分子有650次機會 擊落一架商業客機
and a terrorist has 650 chances to take down a commercial airliner.
所以你想讓我做什么
So, what do you want me to do?
看向另一邊
Look the other way.
拜托 伙計
Oh, come on, man.
如果你不告訴我你知道的一切
By not telling me everything you know,
那就是在保護殺了我朋友的人
you're protecting the people who killed my friends.
我不會浪費時間 用那些審訊技巧
I'm not gonna waste my time with enhanced interrogation techniques.
我只會奪走你的生命
I'm just gonna squeeze the life out of you.
如果你在你死前 想完全卸下自己的負擔
So, if at any point before you die you feel like fully unburdening yourself...
那就眨眼
blink.
- 現在說話 - 好的
- Talk, now. - Okay. Okay.
天啊 讓我喘口氣
Christ. Let me catch my breath.
我們本來應該利用21響禮炮的槍聲
We were supposed to use the gunfire from the 21-gun salute
來掩蓋我們的射擊
to mask our shot.
干掉你和你的團隊成員
Take you and your team down
在任何人搞清楚狀況前離開
and get out of there before anyone knew what was going on.
對于專業槍手來說 賺這錢輕松容易
Easy payday for a couple professional hitters.
- 跟我說些我不知道的事 - 比如
- Tell me something I don't know. - Like what?
蘭斯頓不會一開始就把所有錢都給你
Langston wouldn't give you all the cash up front.
你要在哪里見他拿尾款
Where are you supposed to meet him to get the rest of the money?
皇后區某個破爛街區的 一棟廢棄建筑里
An abandoned building in some shitty neighborhood in Queens.
我可以帶你們去
Look, I-I can take you there.
但我不認識蘭斯頓
But I don't know any Langston.
那是誰雇的你
Then who hired you?
一個叫斯旺的家伙
Some guy called Swan.
收到
Copy that.
迪克森和奧唐納已就位 拉索在街上
Dixon and O'Donnell are in position. Russo's down the street.
所有出口都已覆蓋
All exits are covered.
聽到了嗎  你要是敢亂來 你會后悔的
Hear that? You try anything, you'll be sorry.
你進去拿錢 給我們這地方的信息
But you go in there, get paid, give us the rundown...
里面有多少人 他們帶著什么武器
How many inside, what they're packing...
房間的布局 人都坐在哪里
Layout of the room, where everyone's sitting...
然后我們就放了你 你可以留著錢 懂了嗎
We'll cut you loose and you get to keep the cash. Understood?
好的 隨便吧
Yeah, man. Whatever.
我只希望永遠都不會再見到你們
I just never want to see you people again.
把你的手機給我
Give me your phone.
把這個放在口袋里 這樣我們就能監聽
Keep this in your pocket so we can listen in.
你要是敢做小動作 我們會突然進攻 你就跟他們一起死吧
You try anything, we come in hot and you die with the rest of them.
去吧 蠢貨
Get going, stupid.
我們在想什么
So, what are we thinking?
斯旺去新時代工作
Swan went to work for New Age,
看到了他一直夢寐以求的賺錢機會 然后就接受了
saw a chance to make the kind of money he always dreamed of and took it?
然后呢
Then what?
他跟弗朗茨一起出去玩 他們都在一個城市
He was hanging out with Franzy, them being in the same city and all,
不小心透露了什么 讓弗朗茨產生了懷疑
slipped and said something that made Franz suspicious?
或者他試著拉弗朗茨入伙
Or... tried to get Franz in on it?
心想要養老婆和孩子 他也需要錢
Figured with a wife and kid, he'd need the money, too.
弗朗茨拒絕了
Franz said no,
試圖阻止 打電話給 桑切斯和奧羅斯科求助
tried to stop it, called Sanchez and Orozco for help.
那聽起來對嗎
That sound about right?
我不知道 但如果斯旺真在那棟樓里
I don't know, but if Swan's really in that building,
我也會像對待那家伙一樣對待斯旺
I'm gonna do the same thing I did to that guy.
用手掐住他的脖子 從他嘴里榨出真相
Wrap my hand around his neck and squeeze the truth out of him.
在那之后呢
And after that?
你好
Hello?
有人嗎
Anyone?
字幕翻譯: 匡思穎
創意監督 朝思